Lesson 55, from the Earth.
第55课，来自地球。
Greetings.
问候。
astronomy: n.   天文学
Recent developments in astronomy have made it possible to detect planets in our one milky way and.
天文学的最新发展使得以我们的银河系方式检测行星成为可能。
relative: adj. 相对的
In other galaxies, this is a major achievement because, in relative terms,
在其他星系中，这是一个重大成就，因为从相对角度来看
planets are very small and old knotty-mid light.
行星非常小，旧的缝合光。
Finding planets is proving hard enough,
寻找行星已经足够困难，
infinitely: adv. 无限地，无穷地
but finding life on them will prove infinitely more difficult.
但是找到自己的生活将变得更加困难。
The first question to answer is whether a planet can actually support life.
要回答的第一个问题是行星是否可以真正支持生活。
solar: adj. 太阳系的
In our one solar system.
在我们的一个太阳系中。
Venus: n.   金星, Mars: n.   火星
For example, Venus is far too hot and Mars is far too cold to support life.
例如，金星太热了，火星太冷了，无法支持生活。
Only the Earth provides ideal conditions.
只有地球提供理想的条件。
And even here it has taken more than four billion years for plant and animal life to evolve.
即使在这里，动植物的生命也花费了超过40亿年的发展。
Whether a planet can support life depends on the size and brightness of its star.
行星能否支持生命取决于其恒星的大小和亮度。
That is its Sun.
那就是它的太阳。
Imagine a star up T20 times larger.
想象一下一颗恒星大增加20倍。
Brighter.
更明亮。
Brighter and hotter than our own Sun.
比我们自己的阳光更明亮，更热。
A planet would have to be a very long way from it to be capable of supporting life.
一个星球必须距离它有很长的路要走才能支持生活。
Alternatively, if the star were small,
或者，如果恒星很小，
orbit: n.   运行轨道
the life-supporting planet would have to have a close orbit round it and also provide the perfect.
维持生命的星球必须在围绕它的近端围绕轨道，并提供完美的轨道。
Conditions for life forms to develop.
生命形式发展的条件。
But how would we find such a planet?
但是，我们如何找到这样的星球呢？
At present, there is no telescope in existence that is capable of detecting the presence of life.
目前，没有望远镜能够检测生命的存在。
astronomical: adj. 天文学的
The development of such a telescope will be one of the great astronomical projects of the
这种望远镜的发展将是
21st century.
21世纪。
It is impossible to look for life on another planet using Earth-based telescopes.
使用基于地球的望远镜在另一个星球上寻找生命是不可能的。
generate: v.   产生
Our own warm atmosphere and the heat generated by the telescope would make it impossible to detect.
我们自己的温暖气氛和望远镜产生的热量将使无法检测到。
Objects as small as planets.
像行星一样小的物体。
orbit: n.   运行轨道
Even a telescope in orbit round the Earth.
甚至绕地球的轨道上的望远镜。
Like the very successful Hubble telescope,
就像非常成功的哈勃望远镜一样，
solar: adj. 太阳系的, particle: n.   微粒，粒子
would not be suitable because of the dust particles iron solar system.
由于灰尘颗粒铁太阳系，这将不合适。
Jupiter: n.   木星
A telescope would have to be as far away as the planet Jupiter to look for life in outer space.
望远镜必须与木星的行星一样遥远才能在外太空寻找生命。
solar: adj. 太阳系的
Because the dust becomes thinner the further we travel towards the outer edges of our own solar.
因为灰尘变得越来越小，我们越朝着自己的太阳能的外边缘行驶。
System.
系统。
blot: v.   遮暗
Once we detected a planet, we would have to find a way of blotting out the light from its star.
一旦我们发现了一个星球，我们就必须找到一种从其恒星中射出光的方法。
So that we would be able to see the planet properly and analyze its atmosphere.
这样我们就可以正确看到地球并分析其气氛。
In the first instance, we would be looking for plant life.
首先，我们会寻找植物生活。
bacteria: n.   细菌
Rather than little green men, the life forms most likely to develop on a planet would be bacteria.
最有可能在地球上发展的生命形成而不是小绿色的人，是细菌。
generate: v.   产生, bacteria: n.   细菌, oxygen: n.   氧气
It is bacteria that have generated the oxygen we breathe on Earth.
是细菌产生了我们在地球上呼吸的氧气。
For most of the Earth's history they have been the only form of life on our planet.
在地球的大部分历史中，它们一直是我们星球上唯一的生活形式。
As Earth dwellers, we always cherish the hope that we will be visited by little green men and that we will be able to.
作为地球居民，我们总是珍惜希望我们将被小绿人拜访，我们将能够拜访。
realm: n.   领域
Communicate with them, but this hope is always in the realms of science fiction.
与他们交流，但这种希望始终是科幻小说的领域。
bacteria: n.   细菌
If we were able to discover lowly forms of life like bacteria on another planet,
如果我们能够在另一个星球上发现像细菌这样的卑鄙的生活形式，
it would completely change our view of ourselves.
这将完全改变我们对自己的看法。
As Daniel Golden of NASA observed, finding life elsewhere would change everything.
正如美国宇航局的丹尼尔·戈登（Daniel Golden）所观察到的那样，在其他地方找到生活将改变一切。
No human endeavor or thought would be unchanged by it.
没有人类的努力或思想不会被它改变。